Guide to the Yale Summer and Special Programs Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Summer and Special Programs records
1963-2011
RU 719
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
136
The records consist of program files, correspondence, memoranda, reports, financial papers, and student records documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Summer and Special Programs. Also included are materials on curriculum, conferences, minority programs, budgets, the Lilly Visiting Faculty Program, and the National Endowment for the Humanities.
Yale Summer and Special Programs
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 15-A (YRG 15-A), Central policy and administrative records of Yale summer and special programs.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of program files, correspondence, memoranda, reports, financial papers, and student records documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Summer and Special Programs. Also included are materials on curriculum, conferences, minority programs, budgets, the Lilly Visiting Faculty Program, and the National Endowment for the Humanities.
College students; Summer schools; Universities and colleges -- Administration; University extension; National Endowment for the Humanities; Yale Summer and Special Programs; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students
- Records, 1974-1978; Accession 1980-A-016
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2014
  - Program Files, 1975-1978
    - Accounts, correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Approved programs
      - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Association of Yale Alumni (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Athletic camps (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Biology (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Summer Program and Academic Conferences
      - General
        - 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
        - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Approvals (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Budget (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Conference business (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Fees for conferences and summer use of campus (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Publicity (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Conferences
        - ASME, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - Hill Health, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - Medical Reunion, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - AAUP, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - Computer Science, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
        - ICCA, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
        - Energy and ISPS, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
        - Ethical Issues in Management, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Guideline letters (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Council on East Asian Studies, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Dreyfus Undergraduate Research Program (chemistry), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Dwight Hall (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Economics: National Science Foundation (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Film Series (Summer), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Forestry executives (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Housing
      - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Lilly programs: meetings (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Lilly programs (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Lilly programs
      - Chicago, University of (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Stanford University (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - Visiting Faculty (Box 1, Folder 40 - 42)
    - Minority programs (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Minority programs
      - Budgets (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - Economics (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - Engineering and applied science (Box 1, Folder 46 - 47)
      - New York Foundation (Box 1, Folder 48)
      - Orientation (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities seminars
      - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 50)
      - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 51)
      - Budgets, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 52)
      - Grants, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - National Urban Fellows, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Peabody Museum (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Summer Academic Programs and Conferences (report), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Yale Summer High School (Box 1, Folder 57 - 58)
    - Summer Language Institute (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Summer Language Institute
      - English Language and Orientation Program (Box 2, Folder 60)
      - English Language and Orientation Program, Japanese Students (Box 2)
    - Summer Programs, director (annual report), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Summer Programs: general appropriations, compensatory #886A-53 (Box 2)
    - Summer School of Music and Art (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Summer Term
      - Accounts: limited use
        - Deferred charges, air conditioning (Box 2, Folder 64)
        - Financial aid #991A-32-76907 (Box 2, Folder 65)
        - Financial aid, compensatory #886A-53-76907 (Box 2, Folder 66)
      - Administrative Fees (Box 2, Folder 67)
      - Advance deposits: housing, keys 3991A-32-64401 (Box 2, Folder 68)
      - Budget: fiscal year, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 69)
      - Budget sheets
        - 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 70)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 71)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 72)
      - Budget summaries
        - #644-31 (Box 2, Folder 73)
        - #886-53 (Box 2, Folder 74)
        - #991-32 (Box 2, Folder 75)
      - Compensatory programs #886A-53-87999 (Box 2, Folder 76)
      - Grants
        - #991A-32-57029 [PA-140] (Box 2, Folder 79)
        - #991A-32-57299 [PA-140] (Box 2, Folder 80)
        - #991A-32-57481 [PA-140] (Box 2, Folder 81)
      - Income (Box 2, Folder 83)
      - Old proposals
        - American Dance Festival (Box 2, Folder 84)
        - Association of Ancient Historians (Box 2, Folder 85)
        - Epidemiology Department conference, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 86)
        - National Collegiate Golf Championship (Box 2, Folder 87)
        - New Haven Summer Theatre, Corwith Hamill (Box 2, Folder 88)
        - Miscellaneous
          - 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 89)
          - 1977 (Box 2, Folder 90)
        - Yale-New Haven Teachers Institute, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 91)
      - Receipts #644A-31-00001 (Box 2, Folder 92)
      - Receipts matched with statements #644A-31-00001, 1974 July-1975 August (Box 2, Folder 93)
      - Study account #990A-32-87168 (Box 2, Folder 94)
      - Telephones (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Upward Bound
      - 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 96)
      - General ledger accounts
        - #43635 (Box 2, Folder 97)
        - #43664 (Box 2, Folder 98)
        - #43694 (Box 2, Folder 99)
      - General ledger accounts, gifts #65428 (Box 2, Folder 100)
      - General ledger accounts, State of Connecticut #56989 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities and Lilly Visiting Faculty Program, 1974-1977
    - NEH Summer Seminars, 1977
      - Accounting (Box 3, Folder 102)
      - Catalogue (Box 3, Folder 103)
      - Chronological File (Box 3, Folder 104)
      - General (Box 3, Folder 105)
      - Grants (Box 3, Folder 106)
      - Housing/library (Box 3, Folder 107)
      - Principal investigators
      - Receptions (Box 3, Folder 118)
      - Stipends/travel allowances (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Lilly Visiting Faculty Program (Box 3, Folder 120)
      - Accounting
        - 1975 (Box 3, Folder 121)
        - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 122)
      - Benefits
        - 1975 (Box 3, Folder 123)
        - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 124)
      - Budget, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 125)
      - Early planning (Box 3, Folder 126 - 127)
      - Evaluations
        - 1975 (Box 3, Folder 128)
        - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 129)
        - Letters, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 130)
      - Expenses: receipts, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 131)
      - General
        - 1975 (Box 3, Folder 132)
        - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 133)
      - Housing, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 134)
      - Information, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 135)
      - Originals
        - 1975 (Box 3, Folder 136)
        - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 137)
      - Purchases, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 138)
      - Questionnaires, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 139)
      - Receptions, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 140)
      - Receptions/meetings, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 141)
      - Summer term programs, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 142)
- Student records and office files, 1979-1984; Accession 1986-A-080
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
  - Office Files, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - Language Students
    - A - R, 1979 (Box 2)
    - S - Z, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Science Students, A - Z, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Foreign Students, A - Z, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Language Students
    - A - R, 1980 (Box 4)
    - S - Z, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Other Students, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Student Records
    - A-F, 1981 (Box 6)
    - G - L, 1981 (Box 7)
    - S - Z, 1981 (Box 9)
    - Other, 1981 (Box 9)
    - Foreign Students A - Z, 1981 (Box 10)
  - Mellon Foundation Visiting Faculty Program, 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - Office and Student Files, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
- Student records and office files, 1981-1985; Accession 1987-A-055
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
  - Office Files
    - 1981 (Box 1)
    - 1982 (Box 2)
  - Student Records
    - A - C, 1982 (Box 3)
    - D - H, 1982 (Box 4)
    - I - N, 1982 (Box 5)
    - O - T, 1982 (Box 6)
    - U - Z, 1982 (Box 7)
  - English Language Orientation Program Student Records A - Z, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Visiting Faculty Program, 1983-1984 (Box 8)
  - Mellon Foundation: Visiting Faculty Program, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
- Records of Robin Winks concerning courses taught, 1973-1982; Accession 1987-A-091
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2018
  - Background information, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1975 Course catalog (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1976 Catalog and memos (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1977 Catalog and memos (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Memos, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and memos, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Student records and office files, 1972-1984; Accession 1989-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  - Student Files
  - Administrative Files
    - Connecticut Commission on Aid to Higher Education, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 915)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 916)
    - Advertising, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 917)
    - Yale College--Withdrawn Students, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 918)
    - Chemical Engineering Program, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 919)
    - Development, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 922)
    - Information Bodies, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 923)
    - Engineering Short Term Seminars, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 924)
    - Summer Programs / Yale College Students, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 926)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 927)
    - Budget, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 928)
    - Brochure Distribution, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 929)
    - Staff Meetings, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 930)
    - Proposals, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 931)
    - Elderhostel, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 932)
    - Teachers' Institute, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 934)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 935)
    - Visiting Faculty Program, 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 936)
    - Summer Financial Aid, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 937)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 939)
    - Budget, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 940)
    - North American Association of Summer Sessions Publications on File, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 941)
    - Summer Programs Ads, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 942)
    - Academic Programs, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 943)
    - Tuition, Fees, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 944)
    - Statistics, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 945)
    - Printing Services, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 946)
    - Yale Daily News, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 947)
    - Housing and Dining, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 948)
    - Extra-Curricular Activities Counselors, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 949)
    - Inter-Office Correspondence, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 950)
    - Summer and Special Programs Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 951)
    - Yale Daily News Advertising Rates, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 952)
    - Sterling Associates, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 953)
    - Yale College Council, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 954)
    - U.S. Grant, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 955)
    - Chemical Engineering Program, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 957)
    - British Art, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 958)
    - Drama School Cover letter--complete, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 959)
    - Drama, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 960)
    - Course of Study Committee, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 961)
    - Mailing Lists and Recruitment, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 962)
    - Faculty / Courses, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 965)
    - Advertising, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 966)
    - Statistics / Reports, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 967)
    - Summer and Special Programs Income Student, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 968)
    - Conferences, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 969)
    - Housing and Dining, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 970)
    - Statistical Study, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 972)
    - Yale University Printing Service, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 973)
    - Student, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 974)
    - Drama Program, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 975)
    - Summer Programs Ads, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 976)
    - Inter-Office Correspondence, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 977)
    - Yale Summer Programs Applications, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 978)
    - Advertising, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 979)
    - Yale Summer Programs (Advertising), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 980)
    - Advertising, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 981 - 982)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 983 - 984)
    - The Harvard Crimson, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 985)
    - The New Haven Register, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 986)
    - The Day, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 987)
    - Newsday, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 988)
    - The New York Times, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 989)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 991)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine and Journal, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 992)
    - Our Town Newspaper, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 993)
    - Yale Summer Programs Application Package, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 994)
    - Printing Service, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 996)
    - Financial Planning Auditors' Report, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 997)
    - ELOP, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 998)
    - Advertising, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 999)
    - Advertising, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1000)
    - Statistical Survey, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1001)
    - Posters, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1002)
    - Summer Counselor Applicants, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1004)
    - Mailing Lists for Posters, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1005)
    - Ad Copy, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1006)
    - Recruitment (Summer), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1007)
    - Rates for Summer, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1008)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1009)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1010)
    - Statistics, Enrollments, Tally, etc., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1011)
    - Directory of Yale Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 1012)
    - Calendar Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 1013)
    - Originals, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1014)
    - Ads, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1015)
    - Advance Requests, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1016)
    - Advertising, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1017)
    - Budget, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1018)
    - Expense Reports, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1020)
    - Miscellaneous--Directory, Service, Telephone, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1021)
    - Personnel, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1022)
    - Postage, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1023)
    - Printing Requisitions, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1024)
    - Purchase Requisitions, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1025)
    - Quick Copy, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1026)
    - Service Requests, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1027)
    - Stock Reports, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1028)
    - NAAS S, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1029)
    - Transfers, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1030)
    - 645 A, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1031)
    - 645 B, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1032)
    - 645 C, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1033)
    - 645 D, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1034)
    - 645 E, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1035)
    - 645 F, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1036)
    - 645 G, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1037)
    - 645 J, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1038)
    - 645 K, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1039)
    - 645 X, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1040)
    - Advisory Committee, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1041)
    - Broadsheet, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1042)
    - 1984 Calendar Information (Box 7, Folder 1043)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1044)
    - Chrono, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1045)
    - Forms, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1046)
    - Information Book, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1047)
    - Planning, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1048)
    - ProgramsÂ, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1049)
    - Film Series, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1050)
    - BAC Program for Adults, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1051)
    - BAC Program--Applications, Course Schedule, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1052)
    - BAC Program--Originals, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1053)
    - Elderhostel (Registration Packet), 1983 June (Box 8, Folder 1054)
    - Elderhostel Sample Packet--Registration, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1055)
    - BAC Registration Packet, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1056)
    - Elderhostel Originals, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1057)
    - Elderhostel Activities, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1058)
    - Elderhostel Computer Applications, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1059 - 1060)
    - Elderhostel Courses and Resident, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1061)
    - Correspondence (to go), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1062)
    - Elderhostel Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1063)
    - Elderhostel Registrations--week of Jun 17, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1064)
    - Elderhostel Registrations--week of Jun 24, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1065)
    - 1984 Elderhostel (Box 8, Folder 1066)
    - Elderhostel Correspondence (from Eld. Office), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1067)
    - Elderhostel--Ads, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1068)
    - Advocate Newspapers, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1069)
    - The Boston Globe, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1070)
    - Cass Communications, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1071)
    - The Christian Science Monitor, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1072)
    - Cornell Times Monitor, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1073)
    - Dramatics Magazine, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1074)
    - The Fair -Press, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1075)
    - The Greenwich Times Advocate, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1076)
    - Hartford Courant, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1077)
    - The Harvard Crimson, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1078)
    - Imprint, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1079)
    - The Voice Italian, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1080)
    - Mesa, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1081)
    - New Haven Register Journal Courier, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1082)
    - The New Journal, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1083)
    - Newsday, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1084)
    - New York Review of Books, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1085)
    - New York Times, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1086)
    - The Daily Texan, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1087)
    - Peterson's Guides, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1088)
    - The Philadelphia Inquirer, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1089)
    - Providence Journal Bulletin, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1090)
    - San Francisco Chronicle and Examiner, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1091)
    - School Guide, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1092)
    - Vincent / Curtis Educational Register, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1093)
    - Westchester Rockland Newspapers, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1094)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1095)
    - Yale Daily Magazine, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1096)
    - The Yale Film Quarterly, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1097)
    - The Yale, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1098)
    - Commercial Mailing Lists, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1099)
    - High Schools, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1100)
    - College Board, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1101)
    - Libraries (Local), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1102)
    - Peterson's Guides, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1103)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1104)
- Student records and office files, 1968-1987; Accession 1990-A-041
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
  - Student records, 1986
    - A - C (Box 1, Folder 1 - 207)
    - D - G (Box 2, Folder 208 - 392)
    - H - K (Box 3, Folder 393 - 573)
    - L - O (Box 4, Folder 574 - 773)
    - P - Sq (Box 5, Folder 774 - 973)
    - St - Z (Box 6, Folder 974 - 1134)
  - Director's Information: Summer Language Institute
    - 1978 (Box 7, Folder 1135)
    - 1977 (Box 7, Folder 1136)
    - 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1137)
    - 1975 (Box 7, Folder 1138)
  - Annual Report
    - 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1139)
    - 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1140)
    - 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1141)
  - Summer programs and Conferences Annual Reports, 1968-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1142)
  - New Haven Teachers' Institute
    - 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1143)
    - 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1144)
    - 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1145)
    - 1983 (Box 7, Folder 1146)
    - 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1147)
    - Study
      - 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1148)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 1149)
      - 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1150)
  - Summer Term
    - 1978 (Box 7, Folder 1151)
    - Information, Budget, 1974-1979 (Box 7, Folder 1152)
    - A Statistical Summary of the First Three Years, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 1153)
    - 1977 (Box 7, Folder 1154)
    - Statistics, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1155)
    - 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 1156)
  - Summer programs: other places
    - North American Association of Summer Sessions, 1980-1987 (Box 7, Folder 1157)
    - American University Summer Sessions, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1158)
    - 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1159)
    - Annual Report, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1160)
    - Associates Program, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1161)
    - Booklists and Syllabi, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1162)
    - Bulletin, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1163)
    - Calendar Committee, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1165)
    - Computer Center User Services, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1166)
    - Conferences, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1167)
    - Course of Study Committee, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1169)
    - Custodial Services, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1170)
    - Dwight Hall, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1171)
    - Engineering and Applied Science Research for Juniors, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1172)
    - English Language and Orientation Program, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1173)
    - Faculty, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1174)
    - Financial Aid, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 1175)
    - Forestry, Training Modules, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1176)
    - Housing, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1178)
    - Humanities-Sciences Applications, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1179)
    - Humanities-Sciences Applications Rejected, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1180)
  - Humanities and Social Science
    - Yale Summer Sciences Application Record, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1181)
    - Billing, Cash Receipts, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1182)
    - Courses, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1183)
    - Scholarships, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1184)
    - Enrollment, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1185)
    - Humanities and Science: Grades, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1186)
    - Lectures, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1187)
    - New Haven Summer High School Seminar, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1188)
    - Planning: Alternative Careers for Humanities Ph.Ds, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1190)
    - Humanities and Science: Refunds, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1191)
    - School of Organization and Management, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1192)
    - Sciences, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1193)
    - Starlight Festival, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1195)
    - Summer Language Institute, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1196)
    - Yale College Council, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1197)
    - Women's Caucus, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1198)
    - Summary Report and Inventory, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1199)
    - Annual Report, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1200)
    - Calendar, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1201)
    - Colloquium: Immigrant Experience within Italian-American Culture, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1202)
    - Conferences, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1203)
    - Economic Instruction Workshop, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1204)
    - Engineering and Applied Science, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1205)
    - English Language and Orientation Program, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1206)
    - Experiment in International Living, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1207)
    - Language Laboratory, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1208)
    - NEH Seminars, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1209)
    - Peabody Museum Summer Program, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1210)
    - Summer Language Institute, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1211)
    - Summer School of Music and Art, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1212)
    - Teachers' Preparation Program, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1213)
    - Thor, Inc., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1214)
    - Summer Language Institute, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 1215)
    - Summer Sciences Application Fees, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1216)
    - Budget, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1218)
    - Courses Canceled, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1219)